Oh no.
I'm Karen!
I'm Ducky!
Please!
Yes, that's right.
Today, we have Ms. Fujitani.
Ms. Fujitani asked me to show you around Sendai.
Mr. Fujitani asked me to do a sightseeing tour of Sendai.
But I didn't want to film only a travel show.
so we're going to play tag this time.
Mr. Fujitani really doesn't know anything about Sendai.
so we're going to go around Sendai with the book he's holding in his hand.
We're going to visit the tourist attractions.
And Mr. Tachibana
Mr. Tachibana will follow Mr. Fujitani
Mr. Tachibana is going to catch up with Mr. Fujitani, who has just left.
And if I don't have any clue when I'm chasing him.
If you don't have any hints, you won't be able to catch up with him.
So I'm going to ask you to follow the story on instagram.
I'm going to ask him to post on his insta-story
Mr. Fujitani will post it on his insta-story.
So you can judge the location by looking at it.
Ew!
Please dig.
Okay, because if we don't find it...
I'm not done, am I?
Because it can't change.
On the contrary, once we find it...
Sightseeing ends.
I see.
I'm gonna get out of here.
You're not gonna get away with this, are you?
Mm-hmm. Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, let's make it a rule.
I'm going to enjoy sightseeing in Miyagi today.
I'm going to have some fun.
Let's get going.
Let's go!
I want to eat, but I've always wanted to go to Matsushima.
I've decided to go to Matsushima first.
Okay, I've got one hour left, so I'm already on a time limit, but I'll do my best.
It's 11:48 right now.
But there's a traffic jam, so we can't go any further, and the fact that it's in an hour means that we might catch up with them.
What's a railroad crossing?
Do trains go through here?
Yes.
What?
It's a railroad crossing.
Do trains go through in Sendai?
Sendai has trains, too.
What? Yes, they do.
What?
We've arrived at Matsushima!
I took some pictures.
I'd like to put them on the story.
Here it is!
I'd like to take pictures of summer vacation now.
Okay, I'm on it.
I can't wait to see where Karen will go with this.
I'm going to eat fried oysters.
Good bye!
So, Miyu's first story is up!
It's called "Summer Vacation Now".
I think it's in Matsushima, judging from the background.
I'm going to Matsushima for now!
I'll find you, Miyu!
I'm going to Matsushima!
I'm off to Matsushima!
Yes, ma'am!
Fried persimmons!
Oh, here it is!
Where?
Oh, really.
Let's go here.
I got your campaign card.
I'll order the fried persimmons.
I gave you the story earlier.
I'd like to eat the fried persimmons.
And I'd like to take a picture of the story.
Karen just gave me something.
I'd like to tap it.
Thanks to Karen.
All light blue Jazi.
It's floating.
Gold gun 160 megan
Cute face
Amazing!
Can I send you something?
You want me to send it?
Okay, I'm sending it.
Do you think he'll notice?
Yes, sir.
I'm on my way to Matsushima.
Miyu's insta-story just went up.
She's eating fried oysters.
So it's definitely Matsushima.
And I was just saying to each other in my story.
Where is this?We said to each other, "Where is this?
Many of you told me it was Matsushima.
I'm sure it's in Matsushima.
I'll do my best.
You should go there.
Yes, I'll go there.
Head for Matsushima
I'm eating fried oysters
All light blue jaji
I'm floating
Gold gun 160 megan
Cute face
Amazing!
I'm eating oyster fries
I'm done eating
I'm about to wither away.
It's really bad.
I'm going to Ishinomaki now!
I'm going to Ishinomaki now and go to Abukatsu-san!
I'm going to go to Ishinomaki now and go to Abukatsu.
I'll do my best!
So I arrived at Matsushima.
I came to the same place as Mu's story!
But there is no Mew here.
Anyway, just for the sake of commemoration
I did the same pose.
I don't think I've been there that long.
I'm going to walk around a bit.
Let's go!
In the story now
Mew just ate fried oysters.
Next time, he wants to eat pork cutlet.
The story is up.
I just ate fried oysters
I'm getting in the car.
Anyway...
I've had fried oysters and now I want to eat pork cutlet.
Well, if I can find it, I'll look for it.
Good luck with curry!
Hugh, kanpai!
But since I'm in Matsushima for the time being...
I'm the one who's always looking for something while Miu is out sightseeing.
I don't like it.
I want to eat something.
They're famous for their curry buns.
I want some!
Can we have a strategy meeting while we eat?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to eat some cooked curry buns!
Yes, sir!
So I just got in the car.
Please take a look.
Miu's story
I didn't understand it.
I didn't understand it, but the staff realized that it was a stone roll.
It turns out that Miu Miu goes out to eat pork cutlet with a stone roll!
Amazing!
Let's go to Ishimaki now!
I'm off!
I'll try to find it if I can...
He's the one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
Yes, I've uploaded this story because I've just arrived at Arukazusan. I've uploaded this story even though I'm in Abkatsu now, so he'll be here soon.
He's going to be here soon.
I'd like to give you a picture of this place right now.
Oh no!
Hi again. I left a letter for Karen.
I was going to go to the comic book museum... but I really wanted to eat persimmon crackers... so I'm going back to Matsushima... and then I'm going to Ruler's to eat triangular fried tofu.
I'll do my best.
A scary thing happened, he said he gave a letter saying it was delicious at the exact same place, right in front of me.
I'm really scared, but he gave it to me 42 minutes ago, so I'm sure he's getting closer, so I'm going to go to Ruler's soon after eating Kaki-Senbei.
I'm on my way to Ishinomaki, but the story is up again, and I found a clue at Katsu Abe's.
I'm going to ask him about Miyu's whereabouts.
Wait for me, Katsu Abe, Katsu Abe!
I'm at Katsu Abe's. Did a girl wearing a light blue jersey like mine come here?
Yes, there was.
She said there was a clue here.
It might be over there. Really?
Yes, Miyu's face on a shark panel.
It's funny that Yuko said that.
I didn't ask for any hints.
I don't know...
I dropped something.
To him.
Something Yuko wanted to eat.
I'm going to the mountains to eat it
Please don't look for it. Good night.
Bang bang bang ji?
Oh, fried triangles?
Are you sure it's Mr. Ruler's fried triangles?
Okay, Mr. Ruler.
Shall we go?
I was going to go to Mr. Jogi's.
Until 4:15?
Is he on his way?
I see.I see.
I forgot to eat something.
Forgot something to eat?
Well, then, let's see where Mew-chan is.
I can't read it.
While Mew is eating somewhere...
We'll head to Mr. Jurgi.
We'll ambush Mr. Jogi?
Then we'll head to Mr. Jogi!
I'm off, Mew!
I'm off, Mew-chan!
We've arrived at Matsumari-style!
Oh, I love it so much!
Amazing!
Eh, there's soft ice cream
Matcha green tea.
I want some!
I just went to an oyster cracker shop.
It's closed for business!
I came back just for kaki senbei (oyster crackers)
I guess I came back for oyster crackers.
So I'm going to have some soft-serve ice cream.
I just saw Miyu's story.
I've never seen Miyu...
I've never seen before.
I'm jealous.
What's she eating?
I'm looking for it.
That's the plan.
Miyu called.
I'll take it.
Did you go to the restaurant?
I just got there.
I just got here.
You sure?
Yeah, it's gone.
What did it say?
I'm going to the mountains to eat something Yuna wanted to eat.
Don't look for me.
Good night. - What?
I'll send you a game.
Really? What's that, my present?
That's so sweet of you. It's okay? - No, it's not.
I'll probably get caught, but...
I don't have a choice.
You don't have a choice.
What are you trying to say, that it's too late?
It's late.
No, you'll see.
Can I wait for the DMs then?
He hung up on me.
The ice cream was just a side trip.
Hello? - Hey.
You know... that place I wanted to go to...
I couldn't go because it was closed.
Oh, really?
So I think I'll just head on to the next one.
Where are you going?
I'll give you a hint.
Washington?
A hint? A quiz.
So I can ask the DMs?
Sure.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to send you a DM with a hint.
The car is a Ferris wheel.
It's near the location where the video with the most views was shot.
I'm going to send it.
I have a riddle that Miyu just sent me.
There's a car and an eye, so I'm going to see it by car.
I have a boat and anger
I think Miyu means Poppit is going to Sendai port too.
What will happen?
I'll do my best
Let's go!
I sent you a hint about the clothes.
But you know, we have a strong staff there.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
We're about to arrive at the outlet
I've started to reward them a little.
After the Ferris wheel ride
I'd like to go to HMV
I'm disappointed that I couldn't go to Changqi Mountain.
I'll go there in private this time.
Have you seen the members?
I'd like to make a phone call now.
Hello?
Where are you?
Where do you think?
No, where are you?
Where are you? Yui...
I'm going to tell you where we're going.
Really?
Yo!
This is...
I'm doing it.
They know.I've been made.
Hello?
No, no, no.
You hung up.
Okay, well, now...
I'm really gonna tell you something.
The place we all love.
That place.
It's the only place, right?
In my opinion.
I've got my heart set on a place.
I think I'm going to go there.
Are you sure you want to go? You're not lying, are you?
I know I'm lying.
I'll know in five years.
Grandpa, how did it happen?
They cut me.
He cut me.
Everyone loved it.
He said "that house.
I think he meant Ebean's.
I'm going to go to eBeans.
I'm on my way.
Passing through.
Everybody loves
That place.
Myu just told me about it.
I think he means Ebeans.
Myu's house is
Sendai Castle
Please stay, Sendai Castle
Please stay
please stay
Karen couldn't find me.
I'd like to search for her from behind
I'd like to search for her from behind.
I'll do my best
I gave you a story to lure her in.
Where's EBNP?
That one?
There it is again.
The image quality is terrible.
Where's the cover?
I knew it. I knew it.
I'll put my back to what I just saw.
If the staff can see us, Karen can't.
Don't let the staff know.
You want to go to the package?
I'm going.
She's in the pink. She jumped out.
Go! Go! Go!
Go!
We're at Sendai Castle.
They're filming at the same place.
That's right.
We're filming everything.
Let's film it.
That's great.
I feel like I'm being chased. Scary.
Shall we go to the front? Then put the statue in the background.
It's just like in the photo. I'll just take a quick picture.
Oh, no...
Ending.
Please do.
You think you can beat me just by running away?
That's why I got Mew.
Why do you think it's me, Mew?
I got sidetracked.
That's why you told me, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
How do you do that?
I thought you were dumplings.
What do you mean?
Dumplings.
That's right.
Who won?
I don't know.
Comment section
But you know... it's amazing... the stories...
I was cheered up by everyone's comments.
It was a great project, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I thought there are many places to visit in Sendai.
I could say good things.
That's right.
Miyake, there are a lot of things I really don't know about.
But there are a lot of really good places and delicious food.
I hope everyone can enjoy them.I hope everyone enjoys it as much as I do.
I do.
There are still many attractions that you don't know about.
I hope that we, Ikkinari Talk Co.
I hope that we, Iki-nari Talk, will be able to develop it more and more for everyone.
Well then, shall we close the curtain?
It's so sad.
It's only been one day.
It's true.
It's not like this.
And it's been 15 minutes.
We've been running around for hours.
It's true.
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
If you liked today's video, if you thought it was good, if you thought we did a good job, please click the "Good" button.
I hope you'll click the "Good" button!
Well, that's Karen and Mew from Suddenly Far Away for today's show!
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye bye bye.
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
Good bye.
Adieu.
Bye bye bye.